pcanalysis.net 2013-08-05

# PCAnalysis.net | Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how PCAnalysis.net collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: PCAnalysis.net. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the type of browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome, Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), the time at which you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. We do not only collect any identifiable information in order to optimize and improve our website. 

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information:   
as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process   
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request   
if PCAnalysis.net is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,   
to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

**Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider**  
Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order.This company does not use this information for any other purpose. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**  
In computer language, a cookie is used to store data on a computer's hard drive. Almost all websites utilize cookies to one extent or another. We use third-party cookies, known as "web beacons", to advertise our website using a technology known as Retargeting. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. Certain third party advertisers may collect personal information you provide in fields and forms presented in connection with their ads. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for information you choose to provide in connection with these third party ads. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of the advertisers to learn about their use of your information. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of PCAnalysis.net. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

**Security**  
When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us. In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information. 

**Data Collection and Privacy**  
The Software may collect, store, and periodically send information back to SpeedAnalysis or third party servers. In addition, the Software collects certain registration information during the installation process. Use of certain feedback features in the Software may require you to submit certain personal information such as your name and email address. To the extent that personal data and certain other information about you are collected, such data is subject to our Privacy Policy. 

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

**Contact Information**  
You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at: support@PCAnalysis.net.
